let questions = [
    {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "",
        "answer": ""
    },
    //{
    //    "type": "multiple-choice",
    //    "question": "",
    //    "a": "",
    //    "b": "",
    //    "c": "",
    //    "d": "",
    //    "answer": ""
    //},
    //{
    //    "type": "response",
    //    "question": "Name the alien race that incubated the clones used in the Clone Army?",
    //    "answer": "Kaminoans"
    //}, {
    //    "type": "response",
    //    "question": "While filming 'The Empire Strikes Back,' which actor wasn't sure if he/she wanted to return for a third movie?",
    //    "answer": "Harrison Ford"
    //}, {
    //    "type": "response",
    //    "question": "What special concession did George Lucas make to Samuel L. Jackson when he joined the 'Star Wars' prequels?",
    //    "answer": "Lucas gave Jackson a purple lightsaber."
    //}, {
    //    "type": "response",
    //    "question": "Who said it?\n\"Good against remotes is one thing. Good against the living, that's something else.\"",
    //    "answer": "Han Solo"
    //}, {
    //    "type": "response",
    //    "question": "Who was the actor inside the C-3PO costume?",
    //    "answer": "Anthony Daniels"
    //}, {
    //    "type": "response",
    //    "question": "Who said it?\n\"Adventure. Excitement. A Jedi craves not these things.\"",
    //    "answer": "Yoda"
    //}, {
    //    "type": "multiple-choice",
    //    "question": "Where were the live action scenes for Hoth filmed in 'The Empire Strikes Back'?",
    //    "a": "Glacier National Park in Montana",
    //    "b": "Malmo, Sweden",
    //    "c": "Finse, Norway",
    //    "d": "Meg Griffin",
    //    "answer": "c"
    //}, {
    //    "type": "response",
    //    "question": "What was Princess Leia's last name?",
    //    "answer": "Organa"
    //}, {
    //    "type": "response",
    //    "question": "What was the spacecraft called that Senator Amidala, Qui-Gon Jinn, and Obi-Wan Kenobi used to leave Nabboo in Episode I",
    //    "answer": "Naboo Royal Starship"
    //}, {
    //    "type": "multiple-choice",
    //    "question": "Who was the actor inside the Darth Vader costume in Episodes 4, 5, and 6?",
    //    "a": "David Prowse",
    //    "b": "Peter Mayhew",
    //    "c": "Anthony Daniels",
    //    "d": "James Earl Jones",
    //    "answer": "a"
    //}, {
    //    "type": "multiple-choice",
    //    "question": "When Luke, Leia, and Han Solo are stuck in the trash compactor, what else is in there with them?",
    //    "a": "Gundark",
    //    "b": "Dianoga",
    //    "c": "Wampa",
    //    "d": "Meg Griffin",
    //    "answer": "b"
    //}, {
    //    "type": "response",
    //    "question": "What diminutive actor got his start playing the ewok Wicket in 'Return of the Jedi'?",
    //    "answer": "Warwick Davis"
    //}, 
    {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What is Count Dooku's Sith name?",
        "answer": "Darth Tyranus"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "Who said it?\n\"I'm out of it for a little while, everyone gets delusions of grandeur!\"",
        "answer": "Han Solo"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "Who was the puppeteer that voiced Yoda?",
        "answer": "Frank Oz"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "Who said it?\n\"I suggest a new strategy, R2. Let the wookiee win.\"",
        "answer": "C-3PO"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "When Anakin Skywalker finally became Darth Vader in 'Episode III,' what actor was in the suit?",
        "answer": "Hayden Christensen"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "How did George Lucas first meet Harrison Ford?",
        "answer": "George hired Harrison to build cabinets"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What main character who didn't originally appear in the 1977 'Star Wars' movie was digitally added in the 1997 special edition re-release?",
        "answer": "Jabba the Hut"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What's the name of the famous sound effect that can be heard in every 'Star Wars' movie? (Hint: It's also heard in hundreds of other movies as well)",
        "answer": "Wilhelm Scream"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "On what planet were Padme, Anakin, and Obi-Wan captured and sentenced to death?",
        "answer": "Geonosis"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "Who was the actor inside R2-D2 in Episodes I - VI?",
        "answer": "Kenny Baker"
    }, {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "What location stood in for Tatooine the 1977 film Star Wars: A New Hope?",
        "a": "Death Valley",
        "b": "The Syrian Desert",
        "c": "The Tunisian Desert",
        "d": "The Desert near Yuma, Arizona",
        "answer": "c"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "Who said it?\n\"I'm rather embarrassed, General Solo, but it appears that you are to be the main course at a banquet in my honor.\"",
        "answer": "C-3PO"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "Where did Darth Vader reveal himself to be Luke's father?",
        "answer": "Cloud City"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "In 'Return of the Jedi', Luke Skywalker's lightsaber was green. What color was it in the first two movies?",
        "answer": "Blue"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What type of creature did Han Solo and Luke Skywalker ride on Hoth",
        "answer": "Tauntaun"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "On what planet was the Clone Army created?",
        "answer": "Kamino"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "Whose DNA was used in the creation of the Clone Army?",
        "answer": "Jango Fett"
    }, {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "What creature hung Luke Skwalker upside down in an ice cave on Hoth?",
        "a": "Tauntaun",
        "b": "Wampa",
        "c": "Cookie Monster",
        "d": "Womp Rat",
        "answer": "b"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "Who was the first Jedi to learn how to return from death as a Force Ghost?",
        "answer": "Qui-Gon Jinn"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "Who played Count Dooku?",
        "answer": "Christopher Lee"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "Who said it?\n\"Why, you slimy, double-crossing, no-good swindler.\"",
        "answer": "Lando Calrissian"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What was Anakin Skywalker's mother's name?",
        "answer": "Shmi"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "Which bounty hunter did Han Solo kill in 'Episode IV: A New Hope'?",
        "answer": "Greedo"
    }, {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "Who was the concept artist who worked with George Lucas to create the look and feel of 'Star Wars'?",
        "a": "Frank Frazetta",
        "b": "Ralph McQuarrie",
        "c": "H.R. Giger",
        "d": "Rick Baker",
        "answer": "b"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "Who played Qui-Gon Jinn in Episode I: The Phantom Menace?",
        "answer": "Liam Neeson"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "Who is the queen of Naboo in Episode I: The Phantom Menace?",
        "answer": "Padmè Amidala"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What is the name of the Toydarian who owned Anakin Skywalker?",
        "answer": "Watto"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What race of aquatic sentient beings does Jar-Jar Binks belong to?",
        "answer": "Gungans"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What is the name of the organization that creates a blockade around the peaceful planet of Naboo?",
        "answer": "The Trade Federation"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What planet does Qui-Gon Jinn, Obi-Wan Kenobi, and Padme find Anakin Skywalker on?",
        "answer": "Tatooine"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "Who played Queen Amidala’s decoy and hand-maiden Sabè?",
        "answer": "Kiera Knightley"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What color is Anakin Skywalker’s lightsaber in Episode II: Attack of the Clones?",
        "answer": "Blue"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "Who has Shmi Skywalker married in Attack of the Clones?",
        "answer": "Cliegg Lars"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "Who is the Sith leader of the Separatist movement, and who was his Jedi Master?",
        "answer": "Count Dooku, Yoda was his master."
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What’s the name of the assassin who leads Anakin and Obi-Wan on a wild chase through Coruscant in Attack of the Clones, and who hired her?",
        "answer": "Zam Wesell, who was hired by Jango Fett"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What is Chancellor Palpatine’s malicious Sith alter-ego?",
        "answer": "Darth Sidious"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What is the name of the cyborg Separatist commander who kidnaps Chancellor Palpatine?",
        "answer": "General Grevious"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What does Padmè name her children at the end of Revenge of the Sith, right before she dies?",
        "answer": "Luke and Leia"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What is the name of the order Darth Sidious gives the clone troopers, which means they will kill all Jedi?",
        "answer": "Order 66"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What’s the name of the Wookie home planet?",
        "answer": "Kashyyyk"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What’s the name of the planet where Anakin Skywalker loses the duel against Obi-Wan?",
        "answer": "Mustafar"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What are the children who are being trained as Jedi called?",
        "answer": "Younglings"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "Who was the composer for every film in the Star Wars Saga?",
        "answer": "John Williams"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What are the short junk-collecting aliens on Tatooine called?",
        "answer": "Jawas"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What kind of crystals is the Empire stealing on the planet Jedha?",
        "answer": "Kyber Crystals"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What planet is Galen Erso and his family hiding on at the beginning of Rogue One?",
        "answer": "Lah’mu"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "How does Han win the Millenium Falcon from Lando Calrissian?",
        "answer": "He steals the card Lando hid up his sleeve, and wins the game of sabacc."
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What are Beckett and his gang trying to steal when he first meets Han Solo?",
        "answer": "A shipment of coaxium"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What actor plays Finn?",
        "answer": "John Boyega"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What is the name of the planet Finn, Rose, and BB-8 go to to find someone who can deactivate the hyperspace tracker the First Order has?",
        "answer": "Canto Bight"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "Who plays Kylo Ren?",
        "answer": "Adam Driver"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What type of ship does Poe Dameron successfully lead an attack to destroy at the beginning of The Last Jedi?",
        "answer": "A First Order dreadnought"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What is the name of the superweapon base the First Order is developing in The Force Awakens?",
        "answer": "Starkiller Base"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "Where is Luke Skywalker hiding at the end of The Force Awakens?",
        "answer": "Ahch-To"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "Who is the cantina owner on Takodana who has a lightsaber in her possession?",
        "answer": "Maz Katana"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What’s Poe Dameron’s droid called?",
        "answer": "BB-8"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What planet does Rey live on in The Force Awakens?",
        "answer": "Jakku"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What is the name of Lando Calrissian’s co-pilot in Return of the Jedi?",
        "answer": "Nien Nunb"
    }, {
        "type": "response",
        "question": "What makes Han Solo temporarily blind after he is freed from the carbonite?",
        "answer": "Hibernation sickness"
    }//, {
    //    "type": "response",
    //    "question": "",
    //    "answer": ""
    //}, 
];